A Guide to the Drawings by Oscar Edward Cesare 1912-1943
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Drawings by Oscar Edward Cesare 1912-1943
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
4101
This collection contains ca. 230 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the Library by Mrs. Oscar Edward Cesare of Stanford, Connecticut, on December 19, 1952.
Biographical/Historical Information
Cesare was born in Linkoping, Sweden, in 1885; at age eighteen he moved to Paris to study art. Leaving Paris, he traveled to Buffalo, New York, to continue his studies. Although Cesare's newspaper career began in Chicago, it was in New York City that his first political cartoons appeared in the New York World, followed by The Sun and The Post. In 1920, he became a regular contributor to the Sunday magazine of the New York Times and continued until a few years before his death in 1948.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of ca. 230 cartoons and drawings of Oscar Edward Cesare (1885-1948), 1912-1943, a New York City political cartoonist and artist whose work appeared in many of the leading New York newspapers, such as The Sun, The World, Evening Post, and The New York Times, and in periodicals such as Review of Reviews, Fortune, Colliers, and Life.
Organization
The cartoons have been numbered and arranged in the following groups:
World War Era Cartoons (Oversize Box C-16)
Mexican Affairs (Oversize Box C-16)
United States Politics and Foreign Affairs to 1930 (Oversize Box C-16)
United States Politics and Foreign Affairs to 1930 (Oversize Box C-17)
Franklin D. Roosevelt Era (Oversize Box C-17)
People, in a separate folder in Oversize Box C-17
2 drawings not by Cesare in an oversize folder filed separately from the Cesare cartoons (OS Tray 60)
Contents List
- "Another Sedan Sept 1914" - "The Promise - and The Fulfillment" September 1914 (Oversize C-16)
  Referring to the First Battle of the Marne
- "A Year of This!" July 13, 1916 (Oversize C-16)
  An American soldier waiting to get into the War in The New York Evening Post
- "Somewhere West of Suez" August 18, 1916 (Oversize C16)
  British bulldog chases German soldier back across the Suez Canal in The York Evening Post
- "Ivan's New Rollers" (1916) (Oversize C16)
  The Russian Bear with Brusilov and Letchitzky as its rollers over German soldiers in The York Evening Post
- "Richard Coeur De Lion: 'My Dream Come True'" December 10, 1917 (Oversize C16)
  Featuring the Crusader
- "Peace (German) Hath Her Victories No Less Than War" (March 1918) (Oversize C16)
  Under the terms of the Treaty of Brest-Litovsk Russia has lost 780,000 square kilometers of territory
- "Up and Fight for More Liberty!" August 16, 1918 (Oversize C16)
  A Sword is being offered to Finland by Germany
- "The Strafers" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam swinging a Liberty Loan mallet and an American soldier deliver a telling blow to Germany
- "Both Hands!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam is suspicious of a surrendering German soldier with a knife hidden behind his back
- "A Phoenix" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A Vulture sits atop the world in flames in The New York Evening Post
- "Brothers in Arms" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Australian sailor kicking an U-Boat officer off the deck of his ship at the Adriatic port of Pola
- "The Rising Son, Or, Western Civilization" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Featuring the Japanese bombing of Kiao-Chow on Shantung Province [in China?]
- "How About Home Rule?" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  re Conscription for Ireland
- Austria "Between Two Fires" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Referring to the Czernin Speech and the Pan-German movement
- "The Goat" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Von Arnim on the Flanders Front
- "The Wealth of the Nation" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  An American doughboy
- "The Fool and the Fool Killer" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Autocracy's mace stretched out ready to destroy the unwary peace optimist
- "You Can't Bluff Me; I've Met You Before" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Hoover as a cook refusing to serve a defeated German soldier
- "Aid the Red Cross Here and Have Fewer Crosses Over There" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A Red Cross Nurse pointing to graves in France
- "The Man Who Waits Until Tomorrow is A Friend of Mine" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The Kaiser trying to prevent the purchase of Liberty Bonds
- "Loyalty Day" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Appealing to the patriotism of "German"-Americans
- "Mr. [George Bernard] Shaw - Lecturer" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Featuring Mr. Shaw pointing the way to Utopia with a chained earth beside him
- Wilson warning the Allies "Don't You Make any Mistakes, Either!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
- "Camouflage - German - The Town Lies Before Our Lines" German Official Report" n.d. (Oversize C16)
- "Making the World Safe for Autocracy" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Showing Harden shackled with a Prussian ball and chain and addressing freedom of the press
- "The Cyclone Cellar" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The Prince of Wied has chosen Durazzo as his capital so he can escape if the worst comes
- "Not of This World" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The Crown Prince of Romania and Bride sitting on a cloud on top of the world above the World War
- "This is So Sudden!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The fist of Wilson striking a book of international law
- "When Diplomacy Fails" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Pencil sketch of fallen soldiers
- "Have You Got Yours ?" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Referring to the torch of liberty
- "Secretaries of War" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of Congress, Editors, & Experts, surrounding Secretary Newton D. Baker
- "A German Comparison in Values" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Comparison of the bombing of the dugout of "St. Hindenburg" and the Rheims Cathedral
- "If Germany Wins" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A picture of Lady Liberty crucified on a Maltese Cross
- "The Conspirators" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Hunger and Mutiny attacking a German soldier
- "The Watch on the Rhine" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A shell labelled "Pershing" exploding a gun held by Autocracy with Medievalism in the background
- "The Evolution of the German Eagle" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A reptilian figure with wings
- "Get In Line" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The sale of Liberty Bonds by Uncle Sam
- "The Neighbor" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The tentacles of the German octopus reaching out to ensnare its neighbors along the Baltic Sea
- "Thou Cans't Not Say I Did It; Never Shake Thy Gory Locks At Me" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Referring to the order by Tirpitz for unrestricted submarine attacks on belligerent and neutrals
- "Pardon Me" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The Army pushing Wilson out of the Presidential Chair
- "The Enemy - Alien" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Referring to Wilson, the Court-Martial Bill and Militarism
- "Back Again" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of Uncle Sam puzzling over the news of Americans lost on Marina and a dachshund coming ashore at New London with a periscope attached to its tail
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A group of soldiers standing in a line
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A soldier and another man attempting to catch two fat wealthy characters
- "One continent is under the spell of politicians and the other is most easily hypnotized by [?]" April 30, n.y. (Oversize C16)
  Two American tourists surprised by their vision of Europe
- "Bonds - Which?" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam offers the choice of Prussian manacles or Liberty bonds
- "Are You Sure You're Comfortable?" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Congress making sure the German soldier is warm while the taxpayer's coal bucket is empty
- "Whitewash" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Hertling whitewashes the German military autocracy with his speeches
- "Muckraking" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  by the German soldier
- "From the First Day of the War it was an Immense Business Proposition to Stinnes" n.d. (Oversize C16)
- "Arrogance" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A German soldier throwing down the gauntlet labelled "Hertling Speech"
- " You Help Him" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam, wearing the red cross symbol, and carrying a wounded man
- "Why Don't They Come Across!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A soldier wondering about a newspaper headline, "Liberty Loan is Lagging"
- "Kamerad!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A picture of a German officer and Lenin shaking hands beneath an image of Czar Nicholas in Siberia
- "For Absolute Liberty" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A German soldier throwing off the chains of autocracy
- The German wolf speaking to the Swedish sheep, "We're Going to Be Such Good Friends" n.d. (Oversize C16)
- "We Do Not Say We Will Not Resist the German Invasion - Trotsky" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Germany holding the arm of Trotsky standing on a crumbling bank with civil war and famine below
- "Prussian Toys" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Hindenburg and other German Chancellors holding up Max and a sign "German Peace Offer" in the midst of Allied Shelling
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A feminine figure with wings holding forth the olive branch
- "The Spirit Goes Marching On" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Referring to the passing on of American traditions to foreign born citizens
- "The Comeback" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A German has hung up his wartime uniform and is leaving for business carrying his suitcase full of samples made in Germany
- "Is He Through with Them for Good?" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Prince Max throwing his uniform labelled "Military Autocracy" into the trash can
- "Politicians and the Dove of Peace" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of a group of men prepared to devour the dove on a platter "After the War"
- "A grave in France" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A Crow atop a cross labelled "Militarism" with skulls and a broken sword at the bottom
- "A Battle is a living Thing" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Hindenburg - A German skeleton using a scythe
- Untitled January 30, 1927 (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam with his top hat extended towards Mexico and an eagle perched on his arm holding an olive branch
- Untitled January 8, 1928 (Oversize C16)
  A group of Mexican citizens beneath the American eagle bearing an olive branch
- "Liberty! How Many Crimes Are Committed in Thy Name." n.d. (Oversize C16)
  "The Case of Terrazas" picturing Villa executing father and son near the International Bridge
- "What's the Use!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of [Theodore Roosevelt?] with a pistol at his side labelled Villa, reading about the destruction wrought by the war in Europe
- "A Punitive Expedition" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Wilson leads an expedition against Mexico through the cacti, barefoot and armed with a club
- "Think It Over" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Huerta standing on a mountain summit overlooking flames of murder, bankruptcy, and starvation
- "The Line of Succession" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Showing the succession of Mexican leadership by assassination, including Huerta, Carranza, Obregon, Gonzales, and Zapata
- "The Rough Rider" (1916?) (Oversize C16)
  Theodore Roosevelt riding on the backs of two horses labelled Peace and War toward the White House
- "Coward!" (1916?) (Oversize C16)
  A picture of Theodore Roosevelt leaning over the platform of a train with a sign that says, "Don't Vote For Wilson He Kept Me Out of War!"
- Beginning the Sixth Year "God Helping Me, I Will Not Fail Them, If They Will But Counsel and Sustain Me" (1918?) (Oversize C16)
- "Delighted [?]" June 1, 1924 (Oversize C16)
  A man vigorously shaking hands in a reception line
- Untitled June 22, 1924 (Oversize C16)
  A Woman behind a plow looking back on the destruction of the Great War
- "Do These Things Really Have Any Effect on Elections?" August 10, 1924 (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam Looking at an Exhibit of Political Memorabilia
- "Ever Since Washington Ran For President in a Cocked Hat" August 24, 1924 (Oversize C16)
  Showing a cartoonist at work
- "They Still Think They Make the Issues" October 19, 1924 (Oversize C16)
  Politician on a podium before a poster of "The People" being squeezed by "Capital"
- Untitled February 15, 1925 (Oversize C16)
  Mussolini with advisors
- Uncle Sam "Like Gulliver, goes to Sleep, Takes No Interest in Politics, and Then Wakes Up, Bound to the Ground" March 22, 1925 (Oversize C16)
- Untitled April 19, 1925 (Oversize C16)
  Calvin Coolidge Using a Machine to Shake Hands
- "Russia - Red, Gray and White" August 2, 1925 (Oversize C16)
- "And Now Arises the Radio Orator" August 23, 1925 (Oversize C16)
- "Besides Who But a [?] Woman would Wear Pants?" November 15, 1925 (Oversize C16)
- "Five of Our Elder Statesmen - Gary, Taft, Root, Hughes and Eliot" November 29, 1925 (Oversize C16)
- Uncle Sam with a key to unlock a box labelled "1925" surrounded by representatives of participants in the Great War 1925 (Oversize C16)
- "He would regard prohibition as robbing him of his last liberty" January 31, 1926 (Oversize C16)
- "The Genii In the Bottle" May 22, 1927 (Oversize C16)
  Corruption coming out of a bottle of rum
- "The Gusher" February 19, 1928 (Oversize C16)
  Referring to the Teapot Dome Scandal
- Untitled April 16, 1928 (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam observing people at work almost like automatons
- Untitled March 10, 1929 (Oversize C16)
  Herbert Hoover Fighting A Dragon
- Untitled May 12, 1929 (Oversize C16)
  A Conference between Foch, Haig, Mordacq, Clemenceau, Weygand
- Two drawings of a leader and a group of his advisors being offered a sword of war or the olive branch of peace June 23, 1929 (Oversize C16)
- "Briand - Peace - Smith" September 15, 1929 (Oversize C16)
  A Blacksmith beating his sword into a pruning hook
- "That war which ended in 1918 took millions of men beyond their garden walls....Orientals as well as Western peoples began to think differently. They began to think in terms of the world, instead of within the narrow boundary of the rice fields or the cabbage patch." October 27, 1929 (Oversize C16)
- Untitled November 3, 1929 (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam examining the Capitol dome, which is covered with ants, with a magnifying glass
- "The Watch on the Potomac" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Two drawings featuring George Washington overlooking the capital on his birthday
- "Champion of Civil Service" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A man shielded from Hughes arrow by a shield labelled "A De$erving Democrat" and holding a paper labelled "The Commoner"
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A man carrying a briefcase crossing a busy street in Washington, D.C.
- "The Experience of Prohibition has Failed to Impress the Politician and the Liquor Interests" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A liquor bottle and a politician walking arm in arm overshadowed by a ghostly figure
- "The Secretary of State: 'I Wonder If I Have to Stay Around?'" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of Wilson struggling with many difficult issues while his secretary is leaving with a lecture schedule tucked under his arm
- "The Plum Tree" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  [Wilson?] swinging an axe at a tree labelled "Profit" and "Red Tape"
- "[?] par Excellence" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A picture of a fat Uncle Sam with a vest decorated by dollar signs and a well-dressed German man on "Unter Den Linden" Street
- "Sancho Bryan" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Accompanying Wilson who is tilting at the windmill of business
- "The Peace Junket - I am Leaving Well Satisfied with My Visit - Stimson" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of Stimson returning to American shores from his European visit with results characterized as a balloon
- "Neither of These Are in the Least Satisfactory" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Featuring two portraits of success
- "Our Era Admires Itself Like Narcissus and it Is Disgusted With Itself" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Featuring Narcissus looking into a pool of death and pollution wrought by war
- "These Are American Principles, We Can Stand for no Others" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Uncle Sam pointing to several principles attributed to President Wilson
- "Popularity" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A skunk labelled "Hyphen" interrupts a picnic
- "Josephus: 'A Sunkissed Peach, Mr. President'" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Secretary Daniels offering a lemon labelled "Maine" to President Wilson
- "Science and Nature" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The hand of the U.S. Navy and a hand from the deep wrestle over a submarine
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A reader contemplating a row of busts of famous authors, including Shakespeare, Jefferson, Lincoln, Longfellow, Thoreau, Pope, Swift, and Twain
- "Cherchez La Femme!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  A Woman standing outside the Palais De Justice
- "Another Burden" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Franz Josef weighed down by Italy's condition
- "A Midsummer's Nightmare" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Coal Famine riding on a wagon labelled "Soap" and whipping a man pulling the wagon
- "The Truth, The Whole Truth, and Nothing But the Truth -" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Picture of a man taking an oath with a sword lying before him
- The Torch of Liberty n.d. (Oversize C16)
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C16)
  The Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse waiting in the clouds above a group of men in conference, one of whom is pointing at a globe
- "Missed Him!" n.d. (Oversize C16)
  Prohibition - A "dry" man throws the brick labelled "Vote" at a liquor bottle but misses
- "There's Hope" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  National Prohibition movement in an ark adrift on the sea of war and run aground against the Agricultural Bill, sees the Senate bird returning with the results of a test vote, 36 to 33
- "Safe!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Boston, represented by a pilgrim, has preserved its liquor bottle against the arrows of Billy Sunday
- "They Belong to the Same Gang, Your Honor" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  The House of Representatives, represented by the figure of a prosecutor, group wine, beer, and booze together, before the Senate, represented by the figure of a judge
- "If America could divert the Gulf Stream, northern Europe might go dry" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Uncle Sam is trying to stop the flow of alcohol to Europe with a broom
- "The Danger" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Secretary Bryan juggling the balls of international politics, foreign relations, and neutrality
- "He and Mrs. Asquith make us feel that it is not much" n.d. (Oversize C17)
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A man is washing a blackboard with a map of the United States on it in the form of a camel
- "Perhaps It's Not So Unbecoming After All - And Then It's The Only Kind They Have" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Referring to the 1917 Suffrage Model
- "Senator Borah is the Daddy of Disarmament" n.d. (Oversize C17)
- The Sword of Medical Science attacking "The Dragon" of Infantile Paralysis n.d. (Oversize C17)
- "The Road to Tomorrow" - "Of Course, If Anything Should Happen!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Featuring Theodore Roosevelt in his garage, with a sign "1920 Garage T.R. Owner," watching to see if his war speeches will puncture the tires of the G.O.P. car
- "Hands Off, He's Mine!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Wilson and Charles E. Hughes fighting over Ohio's 24 Electoral Votes
- "Sisyphus" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Wilson pushing the rock labelled "Hard Times" up the mountain away from "Democratic Defeat 1916"
- "Mr. Bryan Says He Will Pay More Attention To The Commoner, Hereafter" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Shown working at his news office while Secretary of State
- "The Senate is Adjourned" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A huge shepherd's crook labelled "Adjournment" is pulling La Follette off the floor
- "A Willing Old Soul" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A Congress loaded down with bills and expenses is willing to take on more from McAdoo
- Uncle Sam as "The Price Fixer" n.d. (Oversize C17)
- "Loosing Patience" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Uncle Sam is "Loosing Patience" with the telegraph office and the proposed strike called for on July 8th
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  [Bryan ?] as a Parrot sitting on a cross bar between a bucket of grape juice and a bucket of olives
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  [Bryan ?] upsets his pitcher of grape juice as he sees Theodore Roosevelt's picture on the front page of the newspaper, "Back Again!"
- "Old Glory" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  "Old Glory" is being torn apart by politicians during the [1920 ?] election
- "Safety First" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  McAdoo and Williams hiding in a U.S. Treasury vault from a bomb labelled "Riggs Bank Charges" while Wilson is out in the open
- "By George! Stealing More of My Stuff!" "Another Political Outrage" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  [Theodore Roosevelt ?] referring to Wilson's Eight Hour Law
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Hays, Penrose, Wilcox, and Perkins riding atop an elephant with 1912 on its leg and pulling a broken steamroller labelled "Republican Machine"
- "Senator Patrick Henry Filibuster: Give Me Liberty to Talk as Much as I Like, Or, Give Me Death!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Referring to the rule to limit debate in the Senate during the war
- "Breaking Into the Game" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Hughes "Breaking Into the Game" being played by Railroad Labor, the Public, Politics, & Congress over the eight hour law and wage increases
- "A Tempest In a Samovar" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Picturing a Russian serving tea from a samovar labelled "Free Speech," and a teacher labelled "Columbia"
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A German soldier sitting on top of a grave with a tombstone reading, "In Memory of the Russian Steam Roller Pax Vobiscum," saying, "And I've Got to Sit Here and Watch It!"
- "A Christmas Present for France" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A British soldier holding a piece of coal from the Lens Coal Fields
- "National Aspirations" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Referring to Romania, with a picture of two fists, "Falkenheyn and Mackensen," holding the army, cattle and grain
- "The Little Nations Are Completely Victorious" n.d. (Oversize C17)
- "The One Who Should Be Hanged" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Railroad Receivership on Haman's Gallows
- "Defending Our National Honor" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  United States Senate, surrounded by the drum of patriotism, anti-repeal, canal tolls, and personal attacks on President Wilson
- "The Boot!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  The Federal Trade Commission giving the hide and shoe profiteers the boot
- "Help Him!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Speaking of Uncle Sam in his general store and quoting Kipling, "If You Can Keep Your Head When All About You Are Losing Theirs and Blaming It On You --"
- "The Vivisectionist" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Operating on the Dove of Peace
- "He Did It!" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A Republican Orator pointing the finger at Wilson because "War" has taken wheat from American families
- "Your Talk Sounds All Right Sam, But What's That Under Your Foot?" n.d. (Oversize C17)
  Free Russia asks, "Your Talk Sounds All Right Sam, But What's That Under Your Foot?" referring to the Outspoken Press
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A Machinist or Industrial Worker Sitting with His Hands Folded, with The Capitol Dome in the background
- Untitled n.d. (Oversize C17)
  A Sea of Human Hands holding [voting ballots ?] outstretched towards a massive statue of a feminine figure
- "The Initial Step is to Simplify the Mechanism" September 14,1930 (Oversize C17)
  A job for the taxpayer to work on Uncle Sam and the economy
- Untitled November 30,1930 (Oversize C17)
  The Statue of Liberty and an Ostrich (labelled "U.S.") with its head stuck in the sand
- "New Dealer Republican Version" and "New Dealer Democratic Version" (ca. 1932) (Oversize C17)
- "Regimentation, Why Should Free Men----?" January 21, 1934 (Oversize C17)
  Comparison of democracy with fascism and communism
- "The Democratic National Chairman Knows Practical Politics are Necessary For Him to Apply if he is to be Expected to Produce the Votes on Election Day" September 2, 1934 (Oversize C17)
  Picture of J.A. Farley and a puppet show
- Untitled October 28, 1934 (Oversize C17)
  Shows a huge sled labeled "New Deal" and "Ride with Roosevelt" pulled by a small donkey
- "The World Fascinates Mr. Roosevelt" January 1935 (Oversize C17)
- Untitled August 11, 1935 (Oversize C17)